{
"questions":[
			{
				"question":"H",
				"response":"Hydrogène"
			},
      {
          "question":"He",
          "response":"Hélium"
      },
      {
          "question":"Li",
          "response":"Lithium"
      },
			{
				"question":"Be",
				"response":"Béryllium"
			},
			{
				"question":"B",
				"response":"Bore"
			},
			{
				"question":"C",
				"response":"Carbone"
			},
			{
				"question":"N",
				"response":"Azote"
			},
			{
				"question":"O",
				"response":"Oxygène"
			},
			{
				"question":"F",
				"response":"Fluor"
			},
			{
				"question":"Ne",
				"response":"Néon"
			},
			{
				"question":"Na",
				"response":"Sodium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Mg",
				"response":"Magnésium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Al",
				"response":"Aluminium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Si",
				"response":"Silicium"
			},
			{
				"question":"P",
				"response":"Phosphore"
			},
			{
				"question":"S",
				"response":"Soufre"
			},
			{
				"question":"Cl",
				"response":"Chlore"
			},
			{
				"question":"Ar",
				"response":"Argon"
			},
			{
				"question":"K",
				"response":"Potassium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Ca",
				"response":"Calcium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Sc",
				"response":"Scandium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Ti",
				"response":"Titane"
			},
			{
				"question":"V",
				"response":"Vanadium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Cr",
				"response":"Chrome"
			},
			{
				"question":"Mn",
				"response":"Manganèse"
			},
			{
				"question":"Fe",
				"response":"Fer"
			},
			{
				"question":"Co",
				"response":"Cobalt"
			},
			{
				"question":"Ni",
				"response":"Nickel"
			},
			{
				"question":"Cu",
				"response":"Cuivre"
			},
			{
				"question":"Zn",
				"response":"Zinc"
			},
			{
				"question":"Ga",
				"response":"Gallium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Ge",
				"response":"Germanium"
			},
			{
				"question":"As",
				"response":"Arsenic"
			},
			{
				"question":"Se",
				"response":"Sélénium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Br",
				"response":"Brome"
			},
			{
				"question":"Kr",
				"response":"Krypton"
			},
			{
				"question":"Rubidium",
				"response":"Rb"
			},
			{
				"question":"Sr",
				"response":"Strontium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Y",
				"response":"Yttrium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Zr",
				"response":"Zirconium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Nb",
				"response":"Niobium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Mo",
				"response":"Molybdène"
			},
			{
				"question":"Tc",
				"response":"Technétium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Ru",
				"response":"Ruthénium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Rh",
				"response":"Rhodium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Pd",
				"response":"Palladium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Ag",
				"response":"Argent"
			},
			{
				"question":"Cd",
				"response":"Cadmium"
			},
			{
				"question":"In",
				"response":"Indium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Sn",
				"response":"Étain"
			},
			{
				"question":"Sb",
				"response":"Antimoine"
			},
			{
				"question":"Te",
				"response":"Tellure"
			},
			{
				"question":"I",
				"response":"Iode"
			},
			{
				"question":"Xe",
				"response":"Xénon"
			},
			{
				"question":"Cs",
				"response":"Césium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Ba",
				"response":"Baruym"
			},
			{
				"question":"La",
				"response":"Lanthane"
			},
			{
				"question":"Ce",
				"response":"Cérium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Pr",
				"response":"praséodyme"
			},
			{
				"question":"Nd",
				"response":"Néodyme"
			},
			{
				"question":"Pm",
				"response":"Prométhium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Sm",
				"response":"Samarium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Eu",
				"response":"Europium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Gd",
				"response":"Gadolinium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Tb",
				"response":"Terbium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Dy",
				"response":"Dysprosium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Ho",
				"response":"Holmium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Er",
				"response":"Erbium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Tm",
				"response":"Thulium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Yb",
				"response":"Ytterbium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Lu",
				"response":"Lutécium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Hf",
				"response":"Hafnium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Ta",
				"response":"Tantale"
			},
			{
				"question":"W",
				"response":"Tungstène"
			},
			{
				"question":"Re",
				"response":"Rhénium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Os",
				"response":"Osmium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Ir",
				"response":"Iridium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Pt",
				"response":"Platine"
			},
			{
				"question":"Au",
				"response":"Or"
			},
			{
				"question":"Hg",
				"response":"Mercure"
			},
			{
				"question":"Ti",
				"response":"Thallium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Pb",
				"response":"Plomb"
			},
			{
				"question":"Bi",
				"response":"Bismuth"
			},
			{
				"question":"Po",
				"response":"Polonium"
			},
			{
				"question":"At",
				"response":"Astate"
			},
			{
				"question":"Rn",
				"response":"Radon"
			},
			{
				"question":"Fr",
				"response":"Francium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Ra",
				"response":"Radium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Ac",
				"response":"Actinium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Th",
				"response":"Thorium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Pa",
				"response":"Protactinium"
			},
			{
				"question":"U",
				"response":"Uranium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Np",
				"response":"Neptunium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Pu",
				"response":"Plutonium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Am",
				"response":"Américium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Cm",
				"response":"Curium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Bk",
				"response":"Berkélium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Cf",
				"response":"Californium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Es",
				"response":"Einsteinium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Fm",
				"response":"Fermium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Md",
				"response":"Mendélévium"
			},
			{
				"question":"No",
				"response":"Nobélium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Lr",
				"response":"Lawrencium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Rf",
				"response":"Rutherfordium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Db",
				"response":"Dubnium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Sg",
				"response":"Seaborgium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Bh",
				"response":"Bohrium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Hs",
				"response":"Hassium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Mt",
				"response":"Meitnerium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Ds",
				"response":"Darmstadtium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Rg",
				"response":"Roentgenium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Cn",
				"response":"Copernicium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Uut",
				"response":"Ununtrium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Fl",
				"response":"Flérovium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Uup",
				"response":"Ununpentium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Lv",
				"response":"Livermorium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Uus",
				"response":"Ununseptium"
			},
			{
				"question":"Uuo",
				"response":"Ununoctium"
			}
    ]
}